20daypersuasion.com 2012-10-03

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

**Purpose**

Your privacy is important to us. We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to protecting your personal information. 

The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for our website. 

We will never give, sell, barter, or rent your email address to any unauthorized third party. 

**Scope**

This privacy statement only covers the information collected on our web site. 

Our web site contains links to other sites and we are not responsible for the privacy practices, actions, or the content of such web sites. 

Our policies and procedures for handling customer information have been created with the understanding that Internet technologies are still evolving and that Internet business methods are continuing to evolve to meet the needs and opportunities of the changing technologies. As a result, our policies and procedures are subject to change without notice. 

**Information collection and use**

Information collected by us is completely on an opt-in basis via our opt in forms on our websites and used solely to provide users with updates or information.

The only information we collect is your email address, name and IP address.

Every email sent out also has an opt-out option. 

**Opt-in/Opt-out & Modifications **

Customers may opt out of receiving notices from us by simply clicking on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of every email sent or by contacting mike@20daypersuasion.com

However, customers may not opt out of receiving information from our business which is essential for maintaining or updating customers' accounts or system information. Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. You may opt-out of all non-essential email and postal mail. 

**Third Party Disclosure of customer information**

We do not provide your individual data to any unauthorized third parties, with the obvious exception of third party business partners. For example authorized parties include our third party credit card processor, autoresponder service and webhost. 

We will not otherwise disclose our customers or subscribers personal and account information unless we have reason to believe that disclosing such information is necessary to identify, make contact with, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing harm or interfering with the rights or property of our business, our customers, or others, or have a good faith belief that the law requires such disclosure. 

We also will not, except for reasons stated below, disclose to third parties the contents of any electronic mail or other electronic communications that we store or transmit for its customers. The circumstances under which we will disclose such electronic customer communications are when: 

\- it is necessary in order to provide service to the customer; 

\- it is necessary to protect the legitimate interests of our business, websites and its customers; 

\- it is required to cooperate with interception orders, warrants, or other legal process that our business determines in its sole discretion to be valid and enforceable; and 

\- it is necessary to provide to a law enforcement agency when the contents are inadvertently obtained by our business and appear to pertain to the commission of a crime. 

We disclaim any intention to censor, edit or engage in ongoing review or surveillance of communications stored on or transmitted through its facilities by customers or others. Our business will, however, review, delete or block access to communications that may harm our business, its customers or third parties. The grounds on which we may take such action include, but are not limited to, actual or potential violations of our Terms And Conditions Policy. 

**Purchases**

When purchasing products and services via our websites, your credit card/payment details and related personal information will be processed by ClickBank.com and its secure servers. In some cases, it will be processed by Paypal.com.

Please refer to ClickBank or Paypal for details of their privacy policy. 

Our website contains links to this and other web sites which our privacy policy does *not apply. Our Privacy Policy cannot be extended beyond our domain, and web pages therein.

Our website contains links to affiliate sites that compensate us for sales made. A portion of any sales will go to help improve the lives of less fortunate people. 

**Children's Guidelines**

Our business and websites requires that all account holders and visitors be 18 years of age or older. If we become aware that any child has accessed our non-publicly available web sites, the account through which the child has gained access will be terminated. 

No information should be submitted to or posted at our web sites by persons under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. All our websites, products and services are open and available only to persons over the age of 18.

If you believe we have collected any information from or about anyone under 13, please contact us immediately.

**Contact Info**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the privacy practices of our business, web sites, or your dealings with us, you may contact us by emailing: 

mikeAT20daypersuasion.com (replace AT with @)
